<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Harshanu</title>
    <link>https://harshanu.space/en/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Harshanu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://harshanu.space/en/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Anupama</title>
      <link>https://harshanu.space/en/page/anupama/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harshanu.space/en/page/anupama/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://harshanu.space/en/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harshanu.space/en/page/about/</guid>
      <description>In a world where paths converge and stories intertwine, there exists a beautiful tale of love, ambition, and shared dreams. Meet Anupama Aili and Harshavardhan Musanalli, two remarkable individuals whose journey transcends borders and professions, proving that love knows no boundaries. With Anupama&amp;rsquo;s prowess in the world of semiconductors and Harshavardhan&amp;rsquo;s expertise as an IT engineer, theirs is a story of collaboration, passion, and unwavering support.
Anupama Aili: Mastering Semiconductors, One Chip at a Time Anupama Aili, a name synonymous with innovation and excellence in the realm of semiconductors, embarked on her journey by pursuing a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harshavardhan Musanalli</title>
      <link>https://harshanu.space/en/page/harsha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harshanu.space/en/page/harsha/</guid>
      <description>Harshavardhan Musanalli is an IT engineer with a passion for travel. He is currently based in Munich, Germany, but he has traveled to over 20 countries in his lifetime. Harshavardhan is always looking for new places to explore and new cultures to experience.
Harshavardhan&amp;rsquo;s love of travel started when he was a child. He would often go on family vacations with his parents and siblings. As he got older, he started traveling on his own.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
